[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Frank William Abagnale, Jr., whose real story inspired the 2002 Spielberg movie Catch Me If You Can, appeared as what character in the movie?", "correct_answer": "A police officer arresting Frank Abagnale, Jr.", "incorrect_answers": ["His characters father", "The FBI agent who is after his character", "Himself"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress won the Academy Award for Best Actress at the 56th Academy Awards on April 9, 1984 in Los Angeles?", "correct_answer": "Shirley MacLaine", "incorrect_answers": ["Meryl Streep", "Jane Alexander", "Julie Walters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was the Praying mantis placed on the Endangered Species List?", "correct_answer": "1976", "incorrect_answers": ["1972", "1970", "1974"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This was the name of the first bubble gum on the market.", "correct_answer": "Dubble Bubble", "incorrect_answers": ["Hubba Bubba", "Wrigleys", "Bazooka"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Leonard Kessler wrote a childrens book called Mr. Pines Purple House.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of meal is the traditional Indonesian dish called Gado-gado?", "correct_answer": "Salad", "incorrect_answers": ["Dessert", "Fried fish", "Soup"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the country below which is NOT located in South America.", "correct_answer": "Panama", "incorrect_answers": ["Surinam", "Chile", "Colombia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long is the female gestation period in wolves?", "correct_answer": "63 days", "incorrect_answers": ["90 days", "25 days", "200 days"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where would you find the Tornio River Valley Euroregion?", "correct_answer": "Sweden / Finland", "incorrect_answers": ["Italy / Slovenia", "Italy / France", "Austria / Italy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The ampere is a physical unit measuring what?", "correct_answer": "Electric current", "incorrect_answers": ["Resistance in wire", "Speed of Electrons", "Voltage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first movie for which Dustin Hoffman received an Academy Award for Best Actor?", "correct_answer": "Kramer vs. Kramer", "incorrect_answers": ["Tootsie", "The Graduate", "Rain Man"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actress played the part of Teresa di Vicenzo in the James Bond film On Her Majestys Secret Service?", "correct_answer": "Diana Rigg", "incorrect_answers": ["Nadja Regin", "Denise Richards", "Tanya Roberts"]}]